Final Project: Hacking Using Rainbow Tables
To understand the project requirements and see how the project works, please refer to the video from the previous session titled "Final Project: Hacking Using Rainbow Tables."
In this project, you are required to implement one task. A sample source.py file that must be used for submission is provided at the bottom of the page. Click the Download File option to download it.
Important Information
The passwords are four-digit numbers ranging from 1000 to 9999.
Submission Requirements
The following requirements must be strictly followed:
• Do not change the name of the function.
• Implement all of your code inside the provided def block.
• Do not write any code outside the function.
• Complete the corresponding task function.
• The final file must be named exactly source.py.
• The file must be compressed as a ZIP archive. RAR format is not accepted.
• The ZIP archive must contain exactly one file, which must be source.py. No other files should be included.
Failure to follow any of these requirements may result in a score of zero by the automated grading system.
Important Note
The online judge uses Python 3.4. In this version, regular dictionaries (dict) do not preserve the order in which items are inserted, which may cause unexpected results when sorting or processing the data.
To avoid this issue, you can use OrderedDict instead of dict. This data structure can be imported from Python's collections module.

Sample CSV Input
danial,99b057c8e3461b97f8d6c461338cf664bc84706b9cc2812daaebf210ea1b9974
elham,85432a9890aa5071733459b423ab2aff9f085f56ddfdb26c8fae0c2a04dce84c
Task Output
danial,5104
elham,9770
-------------------------------------------------------------------------
پروژه ی نهایی : هک از طریق Rainbow


برای مشاهده و فهمیدن صورت پروژه لطفا به ویدیوی جلسه قبل (پروژه ی نهایی : هک از طریق Rainbow) مراجعه کنید.

در این پروژه شما یک task را باید پیاده سازی کنید. نمونه ی فایل source.py که باید برای سابمیت استفاده کنید در پایین صفحه وجود دارد (گزینه دانلود فایل) برای دانلود فایل روی این گزینه کلیک کنید.

 توجه شود که رمز ها از 1000 تا 9999 می باشند. 

به هیچ وجه اسم تابع را عوض نکنید و همه‌ی کدهایی که می خواهید بزنید را در همان def پیاده‌سازی کنید (خارج از def کدی نگذارید) و task تابع مربوطه را کامل کنید و سپس این فایل را حتما با نام  (source.py) و حتما به صورت zip دربیاورید(rar نباشد فقط zip ) و ارسال کنید.(در فایل zip فقط یک فایل باید باشد که همان source.py است و هیچ گونه فایل دیگری در فایل zip قرار ندهید ) 

در صورت رعایت نکردن هر کدام از نکات بالا متاسفانه  نمره شما توسط سیستم صفر خواهد شد .

نکته: سیستم داوری آنلاین از پایتون 3.4 استفاده می کند، در این نسخه دیکشنری ها ترتیب ورود اطلاعات به خود را به یاد نمی آورند و ممکن است در صورت مرتب سازی آنها به نتیجه مطلوب نرسید، برای رفع این مشکل به جای dict از OrderedDict استفاده کنید، این ساختار داده را می توانید از کتابخانه collections در برنامه وارد کنید.

نمونه محتوای یک فایل csv:

danial,99b057c8e3461b97f8d6c461338cf664bc84706b9cc2812daaebf210ea1b9974
elham,85432a9890aa5071733459b423ab2aff9f085f56ddfdb26c8fae0c2a04dce84c
خروجی تسک:

danial,5104
elham,9770
