Sara has recently learned how to type and access the internet. As soon as she went online, she decided to enter a chat room and say hello to everyone.
Sara typed a word in the chat room. If it is possible to delete some of the letters from the word she entered so that the remaining letters form the word hello, then Sara successfully said "hello". Otherwise, she did not.
It is guaranteed that the input consists only of lowercase English letters.
Input
A string containing lowercase English letters.
Example 1:
ahhellllloou
Output
Print YES if hello can be obtained by deleting some characters from the input string; otherwise, print NO.
Example 1 Output
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
سارا به تازگی یادگرفته تایپ کنه و وارد اینترنت بشه. همینکه وارد اینترنت شد تصمیم گرفت وارد یه چت روم بشه و به همه سلام کنه. سارا یه کلمه را توی چت روم وارد کرد. اگه بشه تعدادی از حروف کلمه ای که سارا وارد کرده را حذف کرد و در آخر کلمه ی hello باقی بمونه یعنی سارا تونسته بگه hello در غیر این صورت خیر.


تضمین میشود که ورودی فقط متشکل از حروف کوچک انگلیسی است.

 

ورودی نمونه:

ahhellllloou
خروجی نمونه:

YES
 

 

ورودی نمونه:

hlelo
خروجی نمونه:

NO
