Zargiso, who has recently started learning programming, wants to write a program to determine whether a word is a palindrome or not.
A palindrome is a word that reads the same from left to right and from right to left. For example, Madam is a palindrome, while tehran is not.
Your task is to help Zargiso write a program that checks whether a given word is a palindrome.
Note: Letter case does not matter. For example, both Madam and maDAM are considered palindromes.
Input
A single word.
Output
Print palindrome if the word is a palindrome; otherwise, print not palindrome.
Examples
Input:
madam
Output:
palindrome
Input:
tehran
Output:
not palindrome
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
زرگیسو که تازه با برنامه نویسی آشنا شده می خواد برنامه ای بنویسه که تعیین کنه آیا یک کلمه palindrome هست یا خیر. به کلمه ای میگن palindrome که چه از چپ چه از راست بخونیش یه چیز بشه. مثلا Madam یه palindrome هستش ولی tehran یک palindrome نیست. حالا شما باید به زرگیسو کمک کنی این برنامه رو بنویسه.
لطفا توجه کنید که کوچک یا بزرگ بودن حروف مهم نیست همونطور که گفتیم Madam یک palindrome هست همانطور که maDAM یک palindrome است.

نمونه ورودی:

madam
نمونه خروجی:

palindrome
 

نمونه ورودی:

tehran
نمونه خروجی:

not palindrome
