Officials of the national Kabaddi federation are preparing teams to participate in the World Kabaddi Championships.
According to the rules of the World Kabaddi Championship, each player can participate in a maximum of 5 championship matches. The federation president has gathered all the players of the sport. Each player has participated in a certain number of World Championship matches so far.
A Kabaddi team consists of exactly 3 players. Mr. Shayegan Ariamehr, the president of the federation, wants to form teams such that each selected team can participate together in the World Championship for at least 3 more years.
In other words, each member of a selected team must have participated in the World Championship no more than 2 times so far.
The first line of the input contains an integer n, representing the number of players.
The second line contains n space-separated integers, where each integer represents the number of World Championship matches a player has participated in so far.
Print a single integer representing the maximum number of teams that can be formed under the given conditions.
Example
Input:
6
5 0 4 2 1 0
Output:
1
Explanation
In the given example, the players who have participated in 5 and 4 World Championship matches cannot be selected for a team because they have already exceeded the allowed limit of 2 previous participations.
Therefore, only the four players with 0, 2, 1, and 0 previous participations are eligible.
Since each team requires exactly 3 players, these 4 eligible players can form only
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
مسئولین فدراسیون کبدی کشور در حال آماده سازی تیم هایی برای شرکت در مسابقات جهانی کبدی هستند. طبق قوانین مسابقات جهانی کبدی هر شخص فقط در ۵ مسابقه ی جهانی کبدی می تواند شرکت کند. رئیس فدراسیون تمامی ورزشکاران این رشته را دور هم جمع کرده است، هر بازیکن تا امروز تعدادی بار در مسابقات جهانی شرکت کرده است. تیم های کبدی دقیقا از ۳ نفر تشکیل می شود. حال آقای شایگان آریامهر، رئیس فدراسیون می خواهد تیم هایی تشکیل دهد که در صورت انتخاب شدن هرکدام از آن تیم ها، حداقل بتوانند 3 سال با هم در مسابقات جهانی شرکت کنند (یعنی هرکدام از اعضای یک تیم حداکثر ۲بار در مسابقات جهانی شرکت کرده باشند)

خط اول ورودی شامل عدد n یعنی تعداد بازیکنان کبدی مد نظر است. خط بعدی ورودی شامل n عدد که با space از هم جدا شده اند می باشد که نمایانگر این است که هر بازیکن چندبار در مسابقات جهانی شرکت کرده است. در خروجی یک عدد چاپ کنید که نمایانگر حداکثر تیم های تشکیل شده با شرایط گفته شده می باشد.


ورودی نمونه:

6
5 0 4 2 1 0
خروجی نمونه:

1
در ورودی نمونه داده شده، بازیکنانی که 5 و 4 بازی داشته‌اند، طبق صورت سوال نمی‌توانند در گروهی باشند؛ بنابراین فقط 4 بازیکنی که 0 و 2و 1و 0  بازی داشته‌اند ،می‌توانند در گروه‌ها باشند. با 4 نفر هم تنها می‌توان 1 گروه 3 نفره تشکیل داد. دقت کنید که لازم نیست تعداد حالت‌(جایگشت)هایی را حساب کنید.
