Project: GPA Calculation and Sorting from CSV
In this project, you are required to write a program that reads students' grades from a CSV file, performs several calculations on the grades, and saves the resulting values to output files.
The project consists of five different tasks that you must implement. A template source.py file that must be used for submission is provided at the bottom of the page.
Submission Requirements
The following requirements must be strictly followed:
• Do not change the names of the functions.
• Implement all your code inside the provided def blocks.
• Do not write any code outside the functions, except for importing libraries at the beginning of the file.
• To calculate averages, use only the mean method imported from Python's statistics module.
• Do not round any values.
• All required libraries must be imported only once, at the beginning of the file, and must not be imported inside the functions.
• Complete the corresponding function for each task.
• The final file must be named exactly source.py.
• The file must be compressed as a ZIP archive. RAR format is not accepted.
Failure to follow any of these requirements may result in a score of zero by the automated grading system.
Important Note
The online judge uses Python 3.4. In this version, regular dictionaries (dict) do not preserve the order in which items are inserted, which may cause unexpected results when sorting or processing the data.
To avoid this issue, you can use OrderedDict instead of dict. This data structure can be imported from Python's collections module.

Tasks
Task 1 — Calculate Each Person's GPA
Calculate the average grade of each person and save it together with their name.
The output order must be exactly the same as the order of the input CSV file.
Task 2 — Sort GPAs in Ascending Order
Save each person's GPA together with their name, sorted in ascending order of GPA.
Task 3 — Find the Three Highest GPAs
Save the three highest GPAs together with the names of the corresponding individuals.
Task 4 — Find the Three Lowest GPAs
Save the three lowest GPAs without the names of the corresponding individuals.
Task 5 — Calculate the Overall Average GPA
Calculate and save the average of all individual GPAs.

Sample CSV Input
mandana,5,7,3,15
hamid,3,9,4,20,9,1,8,16,0,5,2,4,7,2,1
sina,19,10,19,6,8,14,3
sara,0,5,20,14
soheila,13,2,5,1,3,10,12,4,13,17,7,7
ali,1,9
sarvin,0,16,16,13,19,2,17,8
Task 1 Output
mandana,7.5
hamid,6.066666666666666
sina,11.285714285714286
sara,9.75
soheila,7.833333333333333
ali,5.0
sarvin,11.375
Task 2 Output
ali,5.0
hamid,6.066666666666666
mandana,7.5
soheila,7.833333333333333
sara,9.75
sina,11.285714285714286
sarvin,11.375
Task 3 Output
sarvin,11.375
sina,11.285714285714286
sara,9.75
Task 4 Output
5.0
6.066666666666666
7.5
Task 5 Output
8.401530612244898
Additional Note
If multiple individuals have the same GPA, their order in the output must be determined alphabetically by name.
For example:
hossein,16.5
mona,16.5
In this case, hossein must appear before mona because their GPAs are equal and hossein comes first alphabetically.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
پروژه محاسبه معدل و مرتب کردن معدل ها از 
csv



در این پروژه شما باید برنامه ایی بنویسید که نمرات افراد مختلف را از یک فایل 
csv 
بخواند ومحاسبات زیر را روی نمرات انجام داده و مقادیر حاصل را در یک فایل ذخیره کند

در این پروژه شما ۵ task مختلف را باید پیاده سازی کنید. نمونه ی فایل source.py که باید برای سابمیت باید استفاده کنید در پایین صفحه وجود دارد (گزینه دانلود فایل) برای دانلود فایل روی این گزینه کلیک کنید.

 

به هیچ وجه اسم تابع ها را عوض نکنید و همه‌ی کدهایی که می خواهید بزنید را در همان def  ها پیاده‌سازی کنید (خارج از def ها کدی نگذارید فقط به جز import کردن کتابخانه ها که همان ابتدای فایل قرار دهید)(برای میانگین گرفتن فقط از متد mean استفاده کنید (این متد از کتابخانه‌ی statistics در فایل زیر import شده است. )) (هیچ کدام از مقدار ها رند نشوند ) (تمام کتابخانه هایی که قصد import کردنشان را دارید فقط یکبار در ابتدای فایل و خارج از def ها قرار دهید و در def ها import نکنید) و به ازای هر task تابع مربوطه را کامل کنید و سپس این فایل را حتما با نام  (source.py) و حتما به صورت zip دربیاورید (rar نباشد فقط zip ) و ارسال کنید. 

در صورت رعایت نکردن هر کدام از نکات بالا متاسفانه  نمره شما توسط سیستم صفر خواهد شد .

نکته: سیستم داوری آنلاین از پایتون 3.4 استفاده می کند، در این نسخه دیکشنری ها ترتیب ورود اطلاعات به خود را به یاد نمی آورند و ممکن است در صورت مرتب سازی آنها به نتیجه مطلوب نرسید، برای رفع این مشکل به جای dict از OrderedDict استفاده کنید، این ساختار داده را می توانید از کتابخانه collections در برنامه وارد کنید.

 

1-معدل هر فرد را محاسبه کند و همراه با نام هر فرد ذخیره کند، ترتیب خروجی اسامی باید دقیقا مساوی ترتیب فایل ورودی باشد. 

2-معدل ها را به ترتیب صعودی همراه با نام هر فرد ذخیره کند. لطفا توجه کنید اگر از dict استفاده می کنید ترتیب معدل ها در آن مشخص نیست برای اطلاعات بیشتر به این لینک مراجعه کنید. https://docs.python.org/3.6/tutorial/datastructures.html#dictionaries

۳-سه معدل برتر را با نام هر فرد ذخیره کند.

۴-سه معدل پایین را بدون نام هر فرد ذخیره کند.

5-میانگین معدل ها را محاسبه و ذخیره کند.

نمونه محتوای یک فایل csv

mandana,5,7,3,15
hamid,3,9,4,20,9,1,8,16,0,5,2,4,7,2,1
sina,19,10,19,6,8,14,3
sara,0,5,20,14
soheila,13,2,5,1,3,10,12,4,13,17,7,7
ali,1,9
sarvin,0,16,16,13,19,2,17,8
 

خروجی تسک اول

mandana,7.5
hamid,6.066666666666666
sina,11.285714285714286
sara,9.75
soheila,7.833333333333333
ali,5.0
sarvin,11.375
 

خروجی تسک دوم

ali,5.0
hamid,6.066666666666666
mandana,7.5
soheila,7.833333333333333
sara,9.75
sina,11.285714285714286
sarvin,11.375
 

خروجی تسک سوم

sarvin,11.375
sina,11.285714285714286
sara,9.75
 

خروجی تسک چهارم

5.0
6.066666666666666
7.5
 

خروجی تسک پنجم

8.401530612244898
 

نکته: به این نکته توجه کنید در هر مرحله اگر معدل چند نفر یکسان بود، ترتیب خروجی باید بر اساس حروف الفبا باشد به طور مثال:

hossein 16.5
mona 16.5
