One day, Sindokht and Irsa were discussing the prices and quality of laptops. Sindokht believes that the more expensive a laptop is, the better its quality should be.
However, Irsa claims that she can find two laptops such that the first one is cheaper than the second one but has higher quality, disproving Sindokht's assumption.
Your task is to help Irsa verify her claim by writing a program.
You are given the specifications of n laptops. The first line of the input contains an integer n, representing the number of laptops.
Each of the next n lines contains two integers:
• The first number represents the price of the laptop.
• The second number represents its quality.
If you can find two laptops satisfying Irsa's condition—where one laptop has a lower price but higher quality than the other—print:
happy irsa
Otherwise, print:
poor irsa
All letters in the output must be lowercase.
Example 1
Input:
2
1 10
7 3
Output:
happy irsa
Explanation:
The first laptop costs 1 and has a quality of 10, while the second laptop costs 7 and has a quality of 3.
Although the second laptop is more expensive, its quality is lower. Therefore, Irsa has successfully found two laptops that disprove Sindokht's assumption.
Example 2
Input:
4
1 5
7 9
5 6
20 30
Output:
poor irsa
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
یه روز سیندخت و ایرسا در حال بحث در مورد قیمت لپ تاپ ها و کیفیت آنها بودند. سیندخت حدس میزنه هرچی یه لپ تاپ گرون تر باشه کیفیت بهتری هم داره. اما ایرسا ادعا می کنه می تونه ۲ تا لپ تاپ پیدا کنه که قیمت اولی از دومی کمتر باشه ولی کیفیتش از دومی بیشتر باشه و بتونه حدس سیندخت را رد کند. حالا شما باید با نوشتن یه برنامه به ایرسا کمک کنید ادعای خودش را بررسی کند.

مشخصات n لپ تاپ به شما داده میشه. خط اول ورودی شامل عدد n هست که تعداد لپ تاپ ها را نشان می دهد. هر یک از n خط بعدی شامل دو عدد می باشد که عدد اول قیمت لپ تاپ را نشان می دهد و عدد دوم کیفیت آن لپ تاپ را. اگه تونستید دو تا لپ تاپ پیدا کنید که شرایط گفته شده توسط ایرسا را داشته باشد چاپ کنید happy irsa در غیر این صورت چاپ کنید poor irsa (لطفا به کوچک بودن حروف توجه کنید تمامی حروف به صورت کوچک نوشته می شوند.)

 

ورودی نمونه:

2
1 10
7 3
خروجی نمونه:

happy irsa
 

در ورودی نمونه لپ تاپ اول قیمت ۱ را دارد و کیفیت ۱۰ (هرچه عدد بزرگتر باشد کیفیت بیشتر است) لپ تاپ دوم قیمت ۷ دارد و کیفیت ۳. خب ایرسا موفق شده است دو لپ تاپ پیدا کند که با اینکه قیمت دومی از قیمت اولی بیشتر است اما کیفیت دومی از کیفیت اولی کمتر است.

 

ورودی نمونه:

4
1 5
7 9
5 6
20 30
خروجی نمونه:

poor irsa
