Mehdi is sending the final list of participants for the Fajr Film Festival closing ceremony to the executive committee so that they can print the entrance cards. However, there is a problem: when the participants registered, they did not enter their names in the standard format.
The standard format requires only the first letter of the name to be uppercase and all remaining letters to be lowercase.
Write a program that reads 10 names from the input and prints their standardized versions in the output.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
مهدی داره لیست نهایی اسامی شرکت کننده در مراسم اختتامیه فیلم فجر رو می فرسته برای کمیته ی اجرایی تا بتونن کارت های ورود رو چاپ کنند. ولی یه مشکلی هست. موقع ثبت نام شرکت کننده ها اسم هاشون رو به صورت استاندارد ننوشته اند. استاندارد یعنی دقیقا حرف اول اسم بزرگ باشه و بقیه حروف اسم کوچک باشد. برنامه ای بنویسید که ۱۰ اسم از ورودی بخواند و استانداردشده ی آنها را در خروجی چاپ کند.
