Programming Exercise: Online Translator
Artadokht is preparing an online translator as part of her university thesis. The translator has a dictionary and must eventually translate a given sentence.
Input
The first line contains an integer n, representing the number of words in the dictionary.
Each of the next n lines contains two words. The second word represents the translation (meaning) of the first word.
The following line contains a sentence. A sentence consists of several words separated by spaces.
Your task is to help Artadokht implement a translator that reads the dictionary and the sentence from the input and translates the sentence.
During the translation process, if a word is not found in the dictionary, the word itself should be printed unchanged.
For more information, refer to the sample input and output.
Important Note
The online judge uses Python 3.4. In this version, regular dictionaries (dict) do not preserve the order in which items are inserted, and sorting them may not produce the expected result in some cases.
To avoid this issue, you can use OrderedDict instead of dict. This data structure can be imported from Python's collections module.
Sample Input
5
hello salam
goodbye khodafez
say goftan
we ma
you shoma
we say goodbye to
you tonight
Sample Output
ma goftan
khodafez to shoma tonight
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
تمرین برنامه نویسی : مترجم آنلاین
آرتادخت برای پایان نامه ی دانشگاهش در حال آماده سازی یک مترجم آنلاین هستش. مترجم آنلاینی که آرتادخت داره آماده می کنه یک دیکشنری داره و در انتها این مترجم باید یک جمله را ترجمه کند.

در خط اول ورودی یک عدد n وجود دارد که نمایانگر تعداد کلمات دیکشنری است. هر یک از n خط بعدی شامل دو کلمه است که نشان می دهد کلمه ی دوم معنی کلمه ی اول است. خط بعدی شامل یک جمله است. یک جمله شامل چند کلمه می باشد که با space از هم جدا شده اند. حال شما باید به آرتادخت کمک کنید و مترجمی بنویسید که دیکشنری و جمله ی مربوطه را از ورودی بخواند و جمله را ترجمه کند. در پروسه ی ترجمه اگر کلمه ای در دیکشنری وجود نداشت خود کلمه را در خروجی چاپ کنید. برای اطلاعات بیشتر به ورودی نمونه و خروجی نمونه توجه کنید.


نکته: سیستم داوری آنلاین از پایتون 3.4 استفاده می کند، در این نسخه دیکشنری ها ترتیب ورود اطلاعات به خود را به یاد نمی آورند و ممکن است در صورت مرتب سازی آنها به نتیجه مطلوب نرسید، برای رفع این مشکل به جای dict از OrderedDict استفاده کنید، این ساختار داده را می توانید از کتابخانه collections در برنامه وارد کنید.

ورودی نمونه:

5
hello salam
goodbye khodafez
say goftan
we ma
you shoma
we say goodbye to you tonight
خروجی نمونه:

ma goftan khodafez to shoma tonight
