Ariamanesh (who was also the name of one of Darius's sons) is annoyed that people on the internet often write words using a mixture of uppercase and lowercase letters.
Because of this, he decided to create a browser that automatically reformats words containing both uppercase and lowercase letters.
The rule is as follows:
• If the number of uppercase letters is greater than the number of lowercase letters, convert the entire word to uppercase.
• Otherwise, convert the entire word to lowercase.
Input
A single word containing uppercase and/or lowercase English letters.
Example
Input:
hasTAM
Output:
hastam
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
آریامنش (اسم پسر داریوش هم بوده) خیلی ناراحته که توی اینترنت ملت وقتی یه کلمه می نویسن توش هم حروف بزرگ استفاده می کنن هم حروف کوچیک. به خاطر همین تصمیم گرفت یه browser بنویسه که کلماتی که هم حروف کوچیک دارن هم حروف بزرگ رو به صورت جدیدی بنویسه، به این صورت که اگر کلمه ای تعداد حروف بزرگش از تعداد حروف کوچیکش بیشتر بود کل کلمه رو با حروف بزرگ می نویسه در غیر این صورت کل کلمه رو با حروف کوچیک می نویسه.


ورودی نمونه:

hasTAM
خروجی نمونه:

hastam
