Saman has recently learned how to work with strings. As a beginner exercise, he is given a relatively simple string manipulation problem, but he needs your help to solve it.
Saman needs to write a program that reads a string of letters from the input and applies the following modifications:
1. Remove all vowels from the string.
2. Print a dot (.) before each consonant.
3. Convert all remaining consonants to lowercase.
The vowels are: a, e, i, o, and u.

سامان تازه کار با رشته ها رو یاد گرفته. برای شروع کار با رشته ها یه سوال نسبتا ساده پیش روی اون قرار گرفته ولی به کمک شما نیاز داره تا بتونه انجامش بده. سامان باید برنامه این بنویسه که یه رشته ی حرفی رو از ورودی بخونه و تغییرات زیر رو در اون اعمال کنه.



۱ - تمامی حروف صدادار رو پاک کنه.

۲ - قبل از هر حرف بی صدا یک نقطه چاپ کنه.

۳ - تمام حروف بی صدا که باقی مانده اند را به صورت کوچک بنویسد.

حروف صدادار aeiou می باشند
