Mr. Zhubin Artabaz, the Secretary-General of the United Nations, is going to conduct a vote to select the members of the organization's executive board.
Dadmehr Jamshidi, who is responsible for the United Nations' computer systems, has written a program to count how many votes each country has received. Your task is to help Dadmehr count the votes.
Input
The first line contains an integer n, representing the total number of votes.
Each of the next n lines contains the name of a country. Country names consist only of lowercase English letters.
Output
Print m lines, where each line contains the name of a country followed by the number of votes it received.
The country names must be printed in alphabetical order.
Important Note
The online judge uses Python 3.4. In this version, regular dictionaries (dict) do not preserve the order in which items are inserted, so sorting a dictionary may not produce the desired result in some cases.
To avoid this issue, you can use OrderedDict from Python's collections module.
Example
Input:
5
sara
hamid
ali
sara
sara
Output:
ali 1
hamid 1
sara 3
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
آقای ژوبین آرتاباز رئیس سازمان ملل متحد هست و قراره راجع به انتخاب هیئت رئیسه یک رای گیری انجام بده! دادمهر جمشیدی که مسئول کامپیوتر سازمان ملل هست برنامه ای نوشته که می شمره هر کشور چند رائ رو کسب کرده. شما قراره با نوشتن برنامه ای به دادمهر کمک کنید تا آراء رو شمارش کنه.

خط اول ورودی شامل عدد n هست که تعداد کل آراء رو نمایش میده. هر یک از n خط بعدی شامل اسم یک کشور می باشد. اسم کشورها از حروف کوچک انگلیسی ساخته شده اند.

در خروجی m خط چاپ کنید که شامل تعداد آراء هر یک از کشورها می باشد. نام کشورها را به ترتیب الفبا در خروجی بنویسید. برای اطلاعات بیشتر به ورودی نمونه و خروجی نمونه مراجعه کنید.


نکته: سیستم داوری آنلاین از پایتون 3.4 استفاده می کند، در این نسخه دیکشنری ها ترتیب ورود اطلاعات به خود را به یاد نمی آورند و ممکن است در صورت مرتب سازی آنها به نتیجه مطلوب نرسید، برای رفع این مشکل به جای dict از OrderedDict استفاده کنید، این ساختار داده را می توانید از کتابخانه collections در برنامه وارد کنید.

ورودی نمونه:

5
sara
hamid
ali
sara
sara
خروجی نمونه:

ali 1
hamid 1
sara 3
